I think there is no denying that a lot
of strange things are happening on
planet Earth.
What? That is a giant flock of ravens or
buzzards going over our house. I have
not seen a giant flock of ravens in
Costa Rica to this point. Have you?
Tel Aviv house? Tel Aviv had a massive
murder of crows leave it last week,
didn't they? Mhm. How many meteors have
hit the United States in the last week?
Eight. Eight meteors have hit the United
States in the last week. An oil refinery
caught fire in Texas. I've never heard
of that happening in my lifetime. That's
kind of an anomaly. All of Australia
turned bright red. The whole sky lit up
bright red. There's been rolling
blackouts all across the globe. Been in
America, number of other countries.
They're talking about a new form of
COVID about to come out. War in the
Middle East, new plagues coming about,
climate disasters. I think there is no
denying that a lot of strange things are
happening on planet Earth. If you'd
refer to Revelation, you'll see a lot of
this mentioned. Seven stars, seven
seals. One of the more interesting
things you might have missed was
something posted on the White House
page.
An AI rendition of Trump Gaza.
Trump Gaza, number one.
>> There is a golden statue of Donald Trump
erected in the Middle East. Golden
future, a brand new life.
When you hear of wars and rumors of
wars, disease, pestilence, signs in the
heavens, you will know the end is near.
You look at the news, you look at the
internet, or up in the sky above my
house. That is absolutely wild. You'll
notice there's a lot of strange things
going on in the world, and I'm not
telling you the end is near. I'm just
telling you to pay attention, look at
the signs, and
that feeling 2 in above your belly
button, it's always either indigestion
or intuition.